Guide to the Leo Lerman papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1923-1995
  - Raynor, William and Chessy Amory, 1983-1993 (Box 18)
  - Raynor, William and Katherine Johnson, 1984-1993 (Box 18)
  - Read, Bill, 1952-1974 (Box 18)
  - Redd, Tyler, 1955-1979 (Box 18)
  - Redgrave, Lynn, 1977-1992 (Box 18)
  - Reed, Harold, 1983-1988 (Box 18)
  - Reed, Marjorie, 1977-1990 (Box 18)
  - Reed, Max, 1982-1988 (Box 18)
  - Reed, Penelope Dudley Ward, 1947-1983 (Box 18)
  - Reichman, Stella, 1972-1992 (Box 18)
  - Rense, Paige, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Resnik, Regina, 1964-1987 (Box 18)
  - Reuterswärd, Carl Fredrik, 1983-1985 (Box 18)
  - Rice, Linda, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Richard, Elaine, 1989-1992 (Box 18)
  - Richardson, Nancy, 1983-1993 (Box 18)
  - Richardson, Tony, 1958-1963 (Box 18)
  - Rickey, Carrie, 1977-1984 (Box 18)
  - Rifield, Phyllis, 1948 1956-1992 (Box 18)
  - Riley, Robert and Maryn, 1976-1983 (Box 18)
  - Ritchard, Cyril, 1959-1972 (Box 18)
  - Riva, John-David, 1988-1990 (Box 18)
  - Riva, Maria, William, Peter and Michael, 1946-1983 (Box 18)
  - Robbins, Jerome, 1957-1990 (Box 18)
  - Robinson, Francis, 1955-1976 (Box 18)
  - Robinson, Jill, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
  - Rodgers, Gaby, 1983-1986 (Box 18)
  - Rodgers, Richard and Dorothy, 1963-1980 (Box 18)
  - Roditi, Edouard, 1945-1983 (Box 18)
  - Rolick, Esther G., 1946-1951 (Box 18)
  - Rome, Florence, 1971-1993 (Box 18)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1956-1983 (Box 18)
  - Rose, Barbara, 1971-1991 (Box 18)
  - Rose, Daniel and Joanna, 1950-1994 (Box 18)
  - Rose, Jon, 1956 (Box 18)
  - Rosenthal, Jack, 1988-1993 (Box 18)
  - Rosenthal, Jean, 1957-1968 (Box 18)
  - Rosier, Michele, 1956-1964 (Box 18)
  - Ross, Herbert, 1950-1993 (Box 18)
  - Ross, Norman, 1956-1983 (Box 18)
  - Ross, Nancy Wilson, 1948-1968 (Box 18)
  - Ross, Steven, 1981-1990 (Box 18)
  - Rossi, Rubrio, 1977-1985 (Box 18)
  - Rotenberg, Bobby, 1983-1989 (Box 18)
  - Rothe, Friede F., 1948-1958 (Box 18)
  - Rothschild, Howard, 1950-1988 (Box 18)
  - Rowles, Polly, 1959-1973 (Box 18)
  - Rusconi, Natale, 1975-1987 (Box 18)
  - S, 1940-1994, (6 Folders) (Box 19)
  - Saal, Rollene, 1969-1985 (Box 19)
  - Saatchi, Doris, 1986-1992 (Box 19)
  - Sabinson, Harvey, 1958-1969 (Box 19)
  - Sachs, Harvey, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Sacks, David, 1985-1988 (Box 19)
  - Saddler, Donald Edward, 1949-1983 (Box 19)
  - Sager, Peter, 1956-1984 (Box 19)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, 1959 (Box 19)
  - Saint-Subber, Arnold, 1951-1984 (Box 19)
  - Sakier, Kay Silver, 1948-1983 (Box 19)
  - Salem, Daniel, 1975-1994 (Box 19)
  - Salsbury, Allen, 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Saltzman, Ellin, 1983-1992 (Box 19)
  - Sanchez, Fernando, 1979-1990 (Box 19)
  - Sanger, Dora Woodyard Durfy Graham, 1955-1980 (Box 19)
  - Sardi, Adele, 1958-1990 (Box 19)
  - Sassano, Anthony, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Saumerez-Smith, John, 1979-1994 (Box 19)
  - Saunder, Remi, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
  - Saz, Ruth, 1950-1987 (Box 19)
  - Scavullo, Francesco, 1974-1983 (Box 19)
  - Schary, Dore, 1962-1965 (Box 19)
  - Schaffhausen, Jane Imbs, 1947-1978 (Box 19)
  - Schanne, Margrethe and Kjeld Noack, 1956-1988 (Box 19)
  - Schippers, Thomas (Tommy), 1953-1967 (Box 19)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur, 1974-1979 (Box 19)
  - Schlesinger, John, 1956-1976 (Box 19)
  - Schofield, Leo, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - Schrijver, Herman, 1965-1971 (Box 19)
  - Schulte, Sarah, 1981-1985 (Box 19)
  - Schwartzbaum, Lisa, 1972-1983 (Box 19)
  - Schwarzenegger, Arnold, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Scopini, Romana, 1983-1991 (Box 19)
  - Scott, Zachary and Ruth Elizabeth Ford, 1946-1964 (Box 19)
  - Seaver, Edwin, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Segal, Martin, 1988-1992 (Box 19)
  - Seifert, Steve, 1983-1987 (Box 19)
  - Seifter, Morton, 1983-1987 (Box 19)
  - Seldes, Marian, 1968-1994 (Box 19)
  - Selwart, Tonio, 1959-1988 (Box 19)
  - Seymour, Anne, 1950-1958 (Box 19)
  - Seymour, May Davenport, 1943-1960 (Box 19)
  - Shapiro, Karl, 1946 (Box 19)
  - Sharaff, Irene, 1953-1976 (Box 19)
  - Shelley, Carole, 1976-1992 (Box 19)
  - Sheraton, Mimi, 1975-1983 (Box 19)
  - Shohet, Jacqueline, 1948-1950 (Box 19)
  - Shulman, Alexandra, 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Sieff, Lois, 1972-1987 (Box 20)
  - Sills, Beverly, 1962-1989 (Box 20)
  - Simeti, Mary Taylor, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - Simmons, Stanley, 1969-1975 (Box 20)
  - Simon, Neil, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Simpson, Beatrice (Babs)1960-198 (Box 20)
  - Simpson, Eileen, 1974-1988 (Box 20)
  - Simpson, Jeffrey, 1984-1994 (Box 20)
  - Simpson, Robert, 1948-1975 (Box 20)
  - Singer, Norman, 1953-1991 (Box 20)
  - Sitwell, Osbert, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Skinner, Cornelia, Otis, 1952-1968 (Box 20)
  - Slesin, Aviva, 1986-1991 (Box 20)
  - Sloan, Sonny, 1969-1991 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Alexis, 1971-1973 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Donald, 1970-1983 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Liz, 1974-1989 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Maggie, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Oliver, 1961-1992 (Box 20)
  - Smyser, Craig Jr., 1968-1971 (Box 20)
  - Snow, Carmel, 1945-1961 (Box 20)
  - Snyder, Robert, 1970-1985 (Box 20)
  - Solomon, Andrew W., 1992-1994 (Box 20)
  - Sondheim, Stephen, 1973-1994 (Box 20)
  - Sonenberg, Benjamin, 1960-1991 (Box 20)
  - Sontag, Susan, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - Soria, Dorle, 1958-1974 (Box 20)
  - Spear, Ruth and Harvey, 1975-1977 (Box 20)
  - Speiser, Martha, 1949-1964 (Box 20)
  - Speiser, Maurice, 1947-1948 (Box 20)
  - Spellman, Erica, 1981-1993 (Box 20)
  - Spiro, David, 1987-1991 (Box 20)
  - Springer, John, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Stacton, David, 1951 (Box 20)
  - Stafford, Jean, 1949-1979 (Box 20)
  - Stafford, Peter, 1978-1983 (Box 20)
  - Stainforth, Diana, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Stalker, Duncan, 1983-1987 (Box 20)
  - Stane, Walker, 1975-1983 (Box 20)
  - Stanfill, Francesca, 1965-1993 (Box 20)
  - Stanfill, Terry, 1982-1989 (Box 20)
  - Starkman, Sandy, 1968-1977 (Box 20)
  - Stavisky, Lotte, 1946-1972 (Box 20)
  - Stalker, Duncan, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Stearns, Nadine Bertin, 1967-1993 (Box 20)
  - Steegmuller, Francis, 1957-1985 (Box 20)
  - Stein, Frances Patiky, 1975-1983 (Box 20)
  - Stein, Jean, 1958-1986 (Box 20)
  - Stein, Mark, 1975-1983 (Box 20)
  - Stephan, Ruth, 1944-1988 (Box 20)
  - Stern, Jane and Michael, 1984-1988 (Box 20)
  - Stevens, Rise, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Stevens, Roger L., 1959-1969 (Box 20)
  - Stewart, Natacha, 1953-1984 (Box 20)
  - Stewart-Gordon, Faith Kaye, 1958-19701958-1969 (Box 20)
  - Stickney, Dorothy, 1963-1976 (Box 20)
  - Stiller, Jerry and Anne Meara, 1984-1993 (Box 20)
  - Stone, Grace (Ethel Vance), 1948-1959 (Box 20)
  - Stone, Peter, 1965-1973 (Box 20)
  - Stouman, Louis Clyde, 1954-1984 (Box 20)
  - Straight, Beatrice, 1936-1977 (Box 20)
  - Strange, Mopsy, undated, 1962 (Box 20)
  - Strasberg, 1958-1963 (Box 20)
  - Straus, Dorothea and Roger, 1957-1989 (Box 20)
  - Straus, Michel, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Stresemann, John-Joachim1950-1983 (Box 20)
  - Stuart, Jan, 1978-1990 (Box 20)
  - Stuber, Christoph, 1985-1992 (Box 21)
  - Stutz, Geraldine, 1985-1991 (Box 21)
  - Styne, Jule, 1962-1993 (Box 21)
  - Styron, William, 1952 (Box 21)
  - Summerhays, Jane, 1986-1989 (Box 21)
  - Susman, Bernard, 1936 (Box 21)
  - Sutherland, Donald, undated (Box 21)
  - Svare, Richard, 1970-1987 (Box 21)
  - Swenson, Swen, 1959-1977 (Box 21)
  - Sykes, Gerald, 1949-1974 (Box 21)
  - Sze, Mai-Mai, 1968-1985 (Box 21)
  - T, 1947-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 21)
  - Tabori, Lena, 1986-1993 (Box 21)
  - Taft, Mimi, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Talbot, Kathrine, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Talese, Nan, 1976-1986 (Box 21)
  - Talmey, Allene, 1942-1985 (Box 21)
  - Tandy, Jessica, 1959-1990 (Box 21)
  - Tarlow, Rose, 1984-1992 (Box 21)
  - Taylor, John, 1964-1990 (Box 21)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1983-1985 (Box 21)
  - Telegrams, 1986-1992, (10 Folders) (Box 21)
    (Transcriptions of Lerman's outgoing telegrams)
  - Tennant, Stephen1961-1964 (Box 21)
  - Tennant, Victoria, 1986-1993 (Box 21)
  - Ter-Arturnian, Rouben, 1955-1981 (Box 21)
  - Terkel, Studs, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Thames, Susan, 1988-1992 (Box 21)
  - Tharp, Twyla, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Curtis, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
  - Thompson, Emma, 1982-1994 (Box 21)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
  - Thorne, John, 1987-1992 (Box 21)
  - Thurman, Betsy, 1947-1973 (Box 22)
  - Tissot, Lin, 1953-1987 (Box 22)
  - Tober, Donald and Barbara, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Todd, Arthur, 1958-1960 (Box 22)
  - Todd, Willena (Toddy), 1952-1969 (Box 22)
  - Toll, Roger, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Tomlin, Lily, Wagner, and Jane, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Tourel, Jennie, 1950-1972 (Box 22)
  - Train, Susan, 1973-1994 (Box 22)
  - Tremaine, Harriet, 1984-1993 (Box 22)
  - Trigere, Pauline, 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - Trilling, Diana and Lionel, 1946-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 22)
  - Trilling, James, 1953-1993 (Box 22)
  - Trombley, Eve, 1956-1989 (Box 22)
  - Trotta, Geri, 1956-1984 (Box 22)
  - Trow, George, 1983-1987 (Box 22)
  - Truman, James, 1989-1992 (Box 22)
  - Tudor, Anthony, 1954-1973 (Box 22)
  - Tunis, John, 1943-1944 (Box 22)
  - Tune, Tommy, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - Tyler, Parker, 1949-1950 (Box 22)
  - Tynan, Kathleen, 1984-1990 (Box 22)
  - Tynan, Ken and Elaine, 1955-1963 (Box 22)
  - U, 1949-1989 (Box 22)
  - Udell, Rochelle, 1990-1993 (Box 22)
  - Ullman, Alex, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Ullman, Robert, 1973-1989 (Box 22)
  - Urbas, Caroline, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - V, 1944-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 22)
  - Valency, Maurice, 1958-1984 (Box 22)
  - Valentine, Helen, 1953-1983 (Box 22)
  - Van, Bobby, 1972-1977 (Box 22)
  - Van Amringe, Judyth, 1978-1989 (Box 22)
  - Vanderbilt, Gloria, 1968-1988 (Box 22)
  - Vanderbilt, Robert, 1952-1983 (Box 22)
  - Van Leer, Wim, 1985-1992 (Box 22)
  - Van Patten, Joyce, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Van Vechten, Carl, 1950-1979, (3 Folders) (Box 22)
  - Van Vechten, Fania Marinoff, 1953-1973 (Box 22)
  - Van Zandt, Pamela, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Vassiliev, Alexandre, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Vaughan, Bernadette, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Vertes, 1949-1959 (Box 23)
  - Vidal, Gore, 1951-1981 (Box 23)
  - Viladas, Pilar, 1988-1993 (Box 23)
  - Vincent, Edgar, 1972-1991 (Box 23)
  - Viracola, Fiddle, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Virga, Vincent, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Vogel, Lucien, 1953 (Box 23)
  - Von Bidder, Alex H., 1984-1992 (Box 23)
  - Von Der Leyen, Katharina, 1987-1989 (Box 23)
  - Von Der Leyen, Marie-Luise, 1985-1992 (Box 23)
  - Von Kersting, Lynn, 1985-1992 (Box 23)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Vreeland, Diana, 1967-1993 (Box 23)
  - W, 1943-1992, (4 Folders) (Box 23)
  - Walker, Dorothea, 1949-1990 (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Reggie (Regina), 1953-1969 (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Tom, 1991-1994 (Box 23)
  - Wallach, Eli, 1989-1992 (Box 23)
  - Walters, Barbara, 1975-1985 (Box 23)
  - Walton, Tony, 1955-1994 (Box 23)
  - Wanger, Shelley, 1983-1994 (Box 23)
  - Ward, Sheila, 1949-1983, (2 Folders) (Box 23)
  - Warhol, Andy, 1951-1984 (Box 23)
  - Warren, Bill, 1958-1959 (Box 23)
  - Warwick, Katherine, 1974-1991 (Box 23)
  - Washburn, Jo, 1943-1945 (Box 23)
  - Washer, Ben, 1957-1978 (Box 23)
  - Waters, Gilbert, 1948-1990 (Box 23)
  - Watts, Helen Hoke, 1944-1973 (Box 23)
  - Webster, David, 1960-1964 (Box 23)
  - Weeks, Edward, 1944-1950 (Box 23)
  - Weidenfeld, George, 1958-1985 (Box 23)
  - Weir, June, 1973-1989 (Box 23)
  - Weisberger, L. Arnold, 1951-1980 (Box 23)
  - Weaver, Ursula and John, 1966-1985 (Box 23)
  - Weaver, William, 1964-1983 (Box 23)
  - Wells, Gully, 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - Wells, Linda, 1988-1992 (Box 23)
  - Welty, Eudora, 1949-1991 (Box 23)
  - Wescott, Glenway, 1953-1973 (Box 23)
  - West, Rebecca, 1955-1981 (Box 23)
  - Westerberg, Verne, 1983-1993 (Box 23)
  - Wharton, Carly, 1957-1980 (Box 23)
  - Wheeler, Hugh, 1959-1965 (Box 23)
  - Wheelock, Dorothy, 1949-1957 (Box 23)
  - Whitehead, Robert, 1955-1994 (Box 23)
  - Whitney, Ruth, 1989-1992 (Box 23)
  - Williams, Maggie, 1959-1994 (Box 23)
  - Williams, Tennessee, undated (Box 23)
  - Williamson, Alix B., 1983-1991 (Box 23)
  - Wickwire, Nancy, 1955-1957 (Box 23)
  - Wilner, Ruth (Mrs. J. Alfred Wilner), 1948-1949 (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Elizabeth, 1988-1991 (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Peter, 1930-1978 (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Phillip, 1967-1971 (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Phyllis, 1977-1984 (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1975-1985 (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Sandy, 1956-1980 (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Victoria, 1984-1992 (Box 24)
  - Windham, Donald, 1970-1989 (Box 24)
  - Winkelman, Anne Weyl, 1958-1985 (Box 24)
  - Winter-Berger, Robert, 1958-1959 (Box 24)
  - Wintour, Anna, 1986-1993 (Box 24)
  - Wisniak, Nicole, 1982-1989 (Box 24)
  - Wittop, Freddy, 1958-1984 (Box 24)
  - Wolf, Billy, 1963-1984 (Box 24)
  - Woodcock, Patrick, 1975-1991 (Box 24)
  - Woodlawn, Holly, 1970-1984 (Box 24)
  - Wormser, Frances, 1935-1986, (3 Folders) (Box 24)
  - Worth, Irene, 1964-1994 (Box 24)
  - Worthington, Marjorie, 1950-1951 (Box 24)
  - Wright, Barbara, 1969-1972 (Box 24)
  - Wright, Clifford, 1946-1988 (Box 24)
  - Wrong, Henry, 1983-1991 (Box 24)
  - Wrong, Polly, 1983-989 (Box 24)
  - Xelowski, Mary Louise, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Y, 1958-1994 (Box 24)
  - Yaffe, James, 1950-1965 (Box 24)
  - Yearwood, Tony, 1989-1991 (Box 24)
  - Yorck, Ruth, 1943-1965 (Box 24)
  - York, Michael and Pat, 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - Yorke, Henry and Dig (aka Henry Green), 1951-1955 (Box 24)
  - Young, Marguerite, 1951-1993 (Box 24)
  - Young, Stanley, 1945-1971 (Box 24)
  - Young, Stark, 1950-1965 (Box 24)
  - Young, Tracy, 1976-1983 (Box 24)
  - Yurka, Blanche, 1951-1968 (Box 24)
  - Z, 1955-1992 (Box 24)
  - Zadkine, Ossip, 1944-1957 (Box 24)
  - Zahedi, Ardeshir, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Zakroff, Zanne, 1986-1992 (Box 24)
  - Zarem, Robert, 1973-1978 (Box 24)
  - Zeffirelli, Franco, 1961-1993 (Box 24)
  - Zevi, Suzanne, 1984 (Box 24)
  - Zimmer, Pierre, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Zines, Harriet, 1945-1984 (Box 24)
  - Zweigenthal, Gail, 1986-1992 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Queries and Submissions, 1984-1994, (5 Folders) (Box 24)
  - Cards from Flowers (Box 25)
  - Cards and Valentines, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Get Well Cards- Eye Operation, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Sympathy Cards- Ida Lerman's Death, 1980, (2 Folders) (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous Cards, (2 Folders) (Box 25)
  - Unidentified Correspondence, (10 Folders) (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous Postcards, (6 Folders) (Box 28)
  - Water Damaged Correspondence (Box 101)
- Series II: Topical Files, 1950s-1990s
  This series contains files related to a number of Lerman's personal and professional interests. He kept topical files on subjects ranging from artists, his friends and associates, travel destinations, and collectibles. A typical topical file contains clippings related to the subject, as well as possibly a small amount of correspondence or memos related to the subject at hand.
  - Adler, Renata (Box 29)
  - Adler, Stella (Box 29)
  - Akers, Karen (Box 29)
  - Alain (Box 29)
  - Alcott, Louisa May (Box 29)
  - Alhadeff, Gini (Box 29)
  - Allen, Woody (Box 29)
  - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 29)
  - American Painting (Box 29)
  - Andrews, Julie (Box 29)
  - Architecture (Box 29)
  - Art, Miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - Art Nouveau and Art Deco (Box 29)
  - Art-- Exhibition Catalogs (Box 42)
  - Arvin, Newton (Box 29)
  - Asher, Gerald (Box 29)
  - Attenborough, David (Box 29)
  - Auden, W.H. (Box 29)
  - Astor, Alice (Box 29)
  - Avedon, Richard (Box 29)
  - Baked Goods (Box 29)
  - Balanchine, George (Box 29)
  - Baldwin, Billy (Box 29)
  - Baldwin, Phillip (Box 29)
  - Barnes, Djuna (Box 29)
  - Barnet, Dick (Box 29)
  - Barrat, Martine (Box 29)
  - Battcock, Gregory (Trylon & Perisphere) (Box 29)
  - Batterberry, Michael (Box 29)
  - Beaton, Cecil (Box 29)
  - Beadle, Ernest (Box 29)
  - Beerbohm, Max (Box 29)
  - Behn, Aphra (Box 29)
  - Bell, Aimee (Box 29)
  - Bellini, Vincenzo (Box 29)
  - Belmont, Mrs. August (Box 29)
  - Berkson, Eleanor Lambert (Box 29)
  - Berliner, M (Box 29)
  - Bernstein, Leonard (Box 29)
  - Biddle, James (Box 29)
  - Birsch, Andrew (Box 29)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth (Box 29)
  - Blair, Ola (Box 29)
  - Blanch, Lesley, (2 Folders) (Box 29)
    (includes a manuscript of The Wilder Shores of Cooking)
  - Book Collecting (Box 29)
  - Book and Magazine Sellers, (2 Folders) (Box 29)
  - Bowles, Paul and Jane (Box 29)
  - Bowls (Box 29)
  - Box, E. (Box 29)
  - Brook, Peter (Box 29)
  - Browning, Robert (Box 29)
  - Bruce, Evangeline (Box 29)
  - Brunhoff, Madame de (Box 29)
  - Buck, Joan Juliet (Box 29)
  - Burnett, Carol (Box 29)
  - Bultman, Fritz (Box 29)
  - Byron, Lord (Box 29)
    (contains a copy of The Great Byron Adventure by Doris L. Moore)
  - Cadmus, Paul (Box 29)
  - Callas, Maria, (10 Folders) (Box 30)
  - Callow, Simon (Box 30)
  - Cantwell, Mary (Box 30)
  - Capote, Truman, (6 Folders) (Box 30)
  - Capote, Truman, (3 Folders) (Box 31)
  - Capote, Truman (oversized) (Box 103)
  - Carey, Peter (Box 31)
  - Carter, Graydon (Box 31)
  - Channing, Carol and Charles Lowe (Box 31)
  - Channing, Stockard (Box 31)
  - Chase, Chevy (Box 31)
  - Cipriani, Arrigo (Box 31)
  - Chester, Louis (Box 31)
  - Children's Books (Box 31)
  - Christmas, (3 Folders) (Box 31)
  - Churchill, Winston (Box 31)
  - Cocteau, Jean (Box 31)
  - Coe, Christopher, (3 Folders) (Box 31)
  - Cohen, Arthur and Elaine (Box 31)
  - Cole, Henri (Box 31)
  - Collectibles-- Catalogs (Box 41)
  - Collectors (Box 31)
  - Collette (Box 31)
  - Comden, Betty, (3 Folders) (Box 31)
  - Condé Nast (Box 31)
  - Coolidge, Calvin (Box 31)
  - Cooper, Arthur (Box 31)
  - Cousins, Norman (Box 31)
  - Coward, Noel (Box 31)
  - Covici, Pascal (Box 31)
  - Cox, Christopher (Box 32)
  - Crathorne, Lord (Box 32)
  - Crisp, Quentin (Box 32)
  - Cukor, George (Box 32)
  - Curtiss, Mina, (3 Folders) (Box 32)
  - Dance Programs and Periodicals (Box 41)
    (including programs from the New York City Ballet, Sadler's Wells Ballet, Ballet Russes, The Ballet Theatre and The Royal Ballet, among others)
  - Dance Programs and Periodicals-- Oversized (Box 102)
  - Danilova, Alexandra (Box 32)
  - Davidson, Victoria (Box 32)
  - Denby, Edwin (Box 32)
  - Delftware (Box 32)
  - Deren, Maya (Box 32)
  - De Wolfe, Elsie (Box 32)
  - Diaghilev (Box 32)
  - D'Anglejan, Didi (Box 32)
  - D'Arezzo, Daniel (Box 32)
  - Dickens, Charles (Box 32)
  - Dickens, Charles and William Makepeace Thackeray (Box 32)
  - Dickey, James (Box 32)
  - Dietrich, Marlene, (2 Folders) (Box 32)
  - Dinesen, Isak (Karen Blixen) (Box 32)
  - Dogs (Box 32)
  - Doyle, Richard (Box 32)
  - Draper, Ruth (Box 32)
  - Dugdale, James (Box 32)
  - Egypt (Box 32)
  - Eight Empresses, (2 Folders) (Box 33)
  - Eliot, T.S. (Box 33)
  - English, Diane (Box 33)
  - Evans, Joni (Box 33)
  - Festival di Asolo (Box 33)
  - Field, Guilliana Taberna de (Box 33)
  - Fitzgerald, Frances (Box 33)
  - Fisher, M.F.K. (Box 33)
  - Fonteyn, Margot (Box 33)
  - Food and Beverage (Box 33)
  - Fortuny, (2 Folders) (Box 33)
  - Fraser, Kennedy (Box 33)
  - French, Herbert (Box 33)
  - Frost, Robert (Box 33)
  - Galleries and Exhibition Announcements (Box 33)
  - Ganz, Julian and Joann (Box 33)
  - Gardiner, Muriel (Box 33)
  - Gardner, Mary (Box 33)
  - Gaudi (Box 33)
  - Geffroy, James (Box 33)
  - Ghosts (Box 33)
  - Gill, Leslie (Box 33)
  - Giselle (Box 33)
  - Goldner, Nancy (Box 33)
  - Gordimer, Nadine (Box 33)
  - Gordon, Ruth (Box 33)
  - Gossip (Box 33)
  - Gould, Stephen Jay (Box 33)
  - Gourmet-- General and Cookbook Reviews (Box 33)
  - Graham, John (Box 33)
  - Graham, Martha, (2 Folders) (Box 33)
  - Graves, Morris (Box 33)
  - Graves, Robert (Box 33)
  - Gray, Clive and Francine (Box 33)
  - Greene, Graham (Box 33)
  - Greene, Stephen (Box 33)
  - Gregory, Andre (Box 33)
  - Gregory, Grisha and Lydia (Box 33)
  - Gritti Hotel (Box 34)
  - Gross, Amy (Box 34)
  - Grossinger, Jennie (Box 34)
  - Guidry, Ron (Box 34)
  - Guimaraes, Dona (Box 34)
  - Haines, William (Box 34)
  - Halberstam, David (Box 34)
  - Halberstam, Eugenia (Box 34)
  - Harris, Ed (Box 34)
  - Harris, Julie (Box 34)
  - Harvey, Georgette (Box 34)
  - Haskett, Molly (Box 34)
  - Hatfield, Hurd (Box 34)
  - Heil, Jane (Box 34)
  - Heilpern, John (Box 34)
  - Hellman, Lillian (Box 34)
  - Hemingway, Mariel (Box 34)
  - Hepburn, Audrey (Box 34)
  - Hepburn, Kate (Box 34)
  - Herlie, Eileen (Box 34)
  - Herman, Jerry (Box 34)
  - Heywood Hill Bookshop (Box 34)
  - Hill-Stead Museum (Box 34)
  - Historical Houses-- American 18th Century (Box 34)
  - Hockney, David (Box 34)
  - Hoke, Helen (Box 34)
  - Holroyd, Michael (Box 34)
  - Hovis, Gene (Box 34)
  - Howard, Jean (Box 34)
  - Hubbard, Graydon (Box 34)
  - Hubert, Karen (Box 34)
  - Hunter, Richard (Box 34)
  - Hutton, Lauren (Box 34)
  - Imbs, Bravig and Valeska (Box 34)
  - Inge, William (Box 34)
  - James, Charles (Box 34)
  - Janeway, Carol (Box 34)
  - Jourdain, Eleanor (Box 34)
  - Jullian, Philippe (Box 34)
  - Jussel, Chris (Box 34)
  - Kafka, Barbara (Box 34)
  - Kazin, Pearl (Box 34)
  - Keaton, Diane (Box 34)
  - Kennedy, Caroline (Box 34)
  - Kennedy Center Honors (Box 34)
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline (Box 103)
  - Kerner, Rose (Box 34)
  - Kiesler, Frederick (Box 34)
  - Kent, Olla (Box 34)
  - King, Stephen (Box 34)
  - Kipling, Rudyard (Box 34)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln (Box 34)
  - Koch, John (Box 34)
  - Kramer, Jane (Box 34)
  - Lambert, Evelyn (Box 34)
  - Landesman Family (Box 34)
  - Laurence, Paula (Box 34)
  - Laurenson, Helen (Box 34)
  - LaTouche, John (Box 34)
  - Lauritzen, Peter (Box 34)
  - Lavery, John (Box 34)
  - Lecesne, James, (3 Folders) (Box 35)
  - Lerman, Jerry (Box 35)
  - Liberman, Alex (Box 35)
  - Lieberson, Jonathan (Box 35)
  - Lindamood, Peter (Box 35)
  - Livingston, Nancy (Box 35)
  - London (Box 35)
  - Longworth, Alice Roosevelt (Box 35)
  - Loos, Anita (Box 35)
  - Loos, Mary Anita (Box 35)
  - Lost and Found Library (Box 35)
  - Lost Ladies (Box 35)
  - Lunt, Alfred, Fontanne, and Lynn (Box 35)
  - MacRae, Joyce (Box 35)
  - Magriel, Paul (Box 35)
  - Mailer, Norman (Box 35)
  - Majolica, (3 Folders) (Box 35)
  - Martin, Judith (Box 35)
  - Marshall, Arthur (Box 35)
  - Martin, Steve (Box 35)
  - Mason, Jerry (Box 35)
  - Massine, Lorca (Box 35)
  - Matera, Barbara (Box 35)
  - Maxwell, William (Box 35)
  - McCallum, June (Box 35)
  - McCann, Mary Ellen (Box 35)
  - McCarthy, Mary (Box 35)
  - McCourt, James (Box 35)
  - McDowall, Roddy (Box 36)
  - McElwaine, Sandra (Box 36)
  - Mellon Polly (Box 36)
  - Meier, Richard (Box 36)
  - Mellen, Polly (Box 36)
  - Menus, (3 Folders) (Box 36)
  - Merchant, Ismail, Ivory, and James (Box 36)
  - Messel, Oliver (Box 36)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent (Box 36)
  - Miller, Arthur (Box 36)
  - Miller, Beatriz (Box 36)
  - Minton (Box 36)
  - Mirabella, Grace (Box 36)
  - Montant, Jane (Box 36)
  - Moore, Marianne (Box 36)
  - Morley, Oliver (Box 36)
  - Morris, Jan (Box 36)
  - Mostel, Zero (Box 36)
  - Muschamp, Herbert (Box 36)
  - Music and Opera-- Programs (Box 41)
  - Nathan, Joan (Box 36)
  - National Theatre of the Deaf (Box 36)
  - Nelson, Indiana (Box 36)
  - Nesbitt, Cathleen (Box 36)
  - Nevelson, Louise (Box 36)
  - New York City Writers Conference (Box 36)
  - Norman, Dorothy (Box 36)
  - Novak, Barbara (Box 36)
  - Obolensy, Serge (Box 36)
  - O'Higgins, Patrick (Box 36)
  - Ophuls, Marcel (Box 36)
  - Oscars (Box 36)
  - Otis, Elizabeth (Box 36)
  - Page, Ruth (Box 36)
  - Paintings (Box 36)
  - Paperweights (Box 36)
  - Parker, Bill (Box 36)
  - Parker, Dorian Leigh (Box 36)
  - Parsons, Betty (Box 36)
  - Passante, Nico (Box 36)
  - Penn, Irving (Box 36)
  - Perl, Jed (Box 36)
  - Pesetsky, Bette (Box 36)
  - Peter the Great (Box 36)
  - Phillips, Eleanore (Box 36)
  - Picasso (Box 36)
  - Picasso, Paloma (Box 36)
  - Pitchers Family (Box 36)
  - Porcelains (Box 36)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne (Box 36)
  - Pritchett, V.S. (Box 36)
  - Proust, Marcel, (3 Folders) (Box 36)
  - Proust, Marcel, (5 Folders) (Box 37)
  - Quidor, John (Box 37)
  - Quilts (Box 37)
  - Radziwill, Lee (Box 37)
  - Railwayana (Box 37)
  - Rare Books and Their Prices (Box 37)